Crone, Michelle; Papers apap101
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Activism, 1973-2000, Undated; 1; 11.35 cubic ft.
  - Seneca Women's Encampment for a Future of Peace and Justice (1983-1988), 1982-1991, Undated; 1.6; 2.6 cubic ft.
    - Non-Registration Forms - S, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - Non-Registration Forms - S, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - Non-Registration Forms - S, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - Non-Registration Forms - T-V, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 14)
    - Non-Registration Forms - W, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 15)
    - Non-Registration Forms - W, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 16)
    - Non-Registration Forms - Y-Z, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 17)
    - Non-Registration Forms - multi-name, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 18)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 19)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 20)
    - Notes, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 22)
    - Nuclear Weapons, 1979; 1980; 1983; 1985-1988; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 21)
    - Other Women's Peace Camps, 1987; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 22)
    - Peace Walk/"Waterloo 54", 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 23)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 24)
    - Planning Notes, 1982 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 25)
    - Postcards, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 26)
    - Postcards, Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 27)
    - Poster (14in by 24in), 1984 (Oversized 5, Folder 3)
    - Press Coverage, 1983 (Oversized 4, Folder 23)
    - Press Releases, 1983; 1985; 1986; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 28)
    - Print of Native Americans and Bison by Susan A. Fuchs[?] "To Michelle My Life Partner (20in by 25in), 1984 (Flat-file 1)
    - Proposals, 1984; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 29)
    - Publications, 1983; 1985; 1987; 1988 (Oversized 4, Folder 24)
    - Publicity, 1983; 1984; 1986; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 30)
    - Reporter's Packet, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 31)
    - Resource Handbook, 1983-1987 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 32)
    - Songs & Chants, 1985; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 33)
    - Speech at Conference [?], 1986 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 34)
    - Staff, 1983; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 35)
    - Stickers, Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 36)
    - T-shirt - Women's Encampment for a Future of Peace and Justice, Undated (Box 25 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - Timelines/Calendars, Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 37)
    - VDT News, 1987-1989 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 38)
    - Video Collective/Women's Media, 1984; 1985; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 39)
    - Vision Statement, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 40)
    - Workshops, Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 41)
    - Writings and Publications, 1983; 1985; 1988; Undated (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 42)
- Events and Productions, 1982-1996, Undated; 2; 10.1 cubic ft.
  Divided into subseries by event or event series. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject, except for Rhythm Fest which is ordered by festival date, then by subject.
  This series consists of material from music festivals and other events that Michelle Crone produced or was involved in organizing.
  - Elword Productions, 1980-1996, Undated; 2.1; 1 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains material concerning Michelle Crone's production company, Elword Productions, which focused on creating events and performances in the Capital Region that would appeal to women and the LGBT community. This includes many files of performers that include biographies, correspondence, published reviews, riders, and technical specifications. Performers were musical groups, comedians, theater performers, and others that generally focused on feminist or lesbian issues. The subseries consists primarily of promotional material, and administrative records for the company are scarce. There is a substantial amount of material from comedian and actress Lea Delaria, whom Crone worked with on numerous occasions.
    - Advertising, Media List, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 43)
    - Aftershow Passes, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 44)
    - Agents, Fleming Tamulevich & Associates, "Artist Updates", 1995; 1996 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 45)
    - Agents, Mary McFaul, 1991 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 46)
    - Articles by Laura Post, 1986; 1992; 1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 47)
    - Business Cards, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987; 1992-1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 49)
    - Elword Mailing List, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 50)
    - "Growing Up Queer in America," Chris Cinque, 1987; 1990 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 51)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 52)
    - Performers, 4 Big Girls, 1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 53)
    - Performers, Altazor, 1989 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 54)
    - Performers, Terry Baum, 1985-1986 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 55)
    - Performers, Begonia, 1988; 1990-1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 56)
    - Performers, Karen Bath, 1988 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 57)
    - Performers, Betty, 1995 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 58)
    - Performers, Billy Tipton Memorial Saxophone Quartet, 1993-1994 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 59)
    - Performers, Angela Bowen, 1988-1991 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 60)
    - Performers, Carolyn Brandy, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 61)
    - Performers, Kelley J. Brower, 1996 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 62)
    - Performers, Maureen Brownsey, 1991-1994 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 63)
    - Performers, Bonnie Buhler-Smith, 1989 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 64)
    - Performers, Sarah Burrill, 1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 65)
    - Performers, Nell Carter, 1995 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 66)
    - Performers, Maggie Cassella, 1991-1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 67)
    - Performers, Teresa Chandler, 1989 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 68)
    - Performers, Kate Clinton, 1988 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 69)
    - Performers, Barbara Cobb, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 70)
    - Performers, Commie Lesbos from Outer Space, 1992 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 71)
    - Performers, Lea DeLaria, 1992-1995 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 72)
    - Performers, Lea DeLaria, John Larroquette Script, 1994 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 73)
    - Performers, Lea DeLaria and Jeanine Strobel, 1983-1985 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 74)
    - Performers, Melanie DeMore, 1990 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 75)
    - Performers, Destiny, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 76)
    - Performers, Disappear Fear, 1992-1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 77)
    - Performers, Alix Dobkin, 1985-1989 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 78)
    - Performers, Dos Fallopia, 1991; 1993-1993 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 79)
    - Performers, Dos Lesbos, 1988; Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 80)
    - Performers, Tracy Drach, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 81)
    - Performers, The Ellen James Society, 1992 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 82)
    - Performers, Melissa Ethridge, ca. 1988; 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 83)
    - Performers, Carole Etzler and Brenda Chambers, 1986 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 84)
    - Performers, Alice Evergreen, Undated (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 85)
    - Performers, Sue Fink, 1985 (Box 7 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 86)
    - Performers, Five Lesbian Brothers, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 1)
    - Performers, Fliers, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 2)
    - Performers, Garden Variety Lesbian Variety Show, 1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 3)
    - Performers, Girls in the Nose, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 4)
    - Performers, Marga Gomez, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 5)
    - Performers, Monica Grant, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 6)
    - Performers, Lisa Gray, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 7)
    - Performers, Michael Greer, 1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 8)
    - Performers, Kristen Hall, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 9)
    - Performers, Hawkins and Delear, 1986-1987 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 10)
    - Performers, Susan Herrick, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 11)
    - Performers, Ubaka Hill, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 12)
    - Performers, Helen Hooke, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 13)
    - Performers, Cheryl Jacobs, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 14)
    - Performers, JEB (Joan E. Biron), 1986 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 15)
    - Performers, Lisa Koch, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 16)
    - Performers, Lynn Lavner, 1986 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 17)
    - Performers, Laura Love, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 18)
    - Performers, The Maggie & Maggie Show, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 19)
    - Performers, Maul Girls, 1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 20)
    - Performers, Marla BB, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 21)
    - Performers, Diedre McCalla, 1985; 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 22)
    - Performers, Muriel Miguel, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 23)
    - Performers, Melanie Monsur, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 24)
    - Performers, Lynda Montgomery, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 25)
    - Performers, Maggie Moore, 1992; 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 26)
    - Performers, Faith Nolan, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 27)
    - Performers, Olatunji, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 28)
    - Kristen O'Shee, 1994-1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 29)
    - Performers, Pele Juju, 1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 30)
    - Performers, Linee Perroncel, 1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 31)
    - Performers, Janice Perry, 1986; 1988-1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 32)
    - Performers, Marjy Plant, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 33)
    - Performers, Georgia Ragsdale, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 34)
    - Performers, Red Flag, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 35)
    - Performers, Rhythm Express, 1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 36)
    - Performers, Karen Ripley, 1994-1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 37)
    - Performers, Betsy Salkind, 1992-1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 38)
    - Performers, Sally Landers and the Fixations, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 39)
    - Performers, She Is, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 40)
    - Performers, Sisters on Stage (S.O.S.), 1992; Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 41)
    - Performers, Slightly Tortured Music, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 42)
    - Performers, Judith Sloan, 1983; 1985-1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 43)
    - Performers, Smith and Bakken, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 44)
    - Performers, Sorrel Doris Hays, 1986 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 45)
    - Performers, Strangers in Paradise, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 46)
    - Performers, Suede, 1987-1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 47)
    - Performers, Ten Percent Review, 1985-1987 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 48)
    - Performers, Lucie Blue Tremblay, 1986 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 49)
    - Performers, Teresa Trull, 1988; 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 50)
    - Performers, Sophie Tucker, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 51)
    - Performers, Two Nice Girls, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 52)
    - Performers, Two Spirited Thunder People, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 53)
    - Performers, Edwina Tyler, 1985; 1992-1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 54)
    - Performers, Robin Tyler, 1980; 1988; 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 55)
    - Performers, Venus Envy, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 56)
    - Performers, Oliver Wadsworth, 1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 57)
    - Performers, Kathryn Warner, 1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 58)
    - Performers, The Washington Sisters, 1987-1988; 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 59)
    - Performers, Sam Weis, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 60)
    - Performers, Karen Williams, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 61)
    - Performers, Wise Guys, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 62)
    - Performers, The Wyrd Sisters, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 63)
    - Performers, Yagottawanna, 1992-1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 64)
    - Performers, Yer Girlfriend, 1990 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 65)
    - Performers, Leah Zicari, 1991 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 66)
    - Phone Messages, 1989; Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 67)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 68)
    - Rough Around the Edges, by Beth Wood (theatrical script), Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 69)
    - Skeletons are Crying, by Kathleen Mahoney (theatrical script), Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 70)
    - Somerville Theater, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 71)
    - Suede vs. Columbia Records, subpoena, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 72)
    - Technicians, Hanna Vorlicek, 1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 73)
    - Tele Personal, by Margaret Webb (theatrical script), 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 74)
    - Theatrical Scripts, 1981; Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 75)
    - Walk and Squawk Productions, 1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 76)
    - Will You Be My Angel?, by Penny Jacqueline White (theatrical script), 1995 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 77)
  - Full Circle Festival: Equinox '89, 1989; Undated; 2.2; 0.5 cubic ft.
    This subseries includes correspondence, handwritten notes, forms, schedules, bills, financial records. Performers and presenters files consist of biographies, correspondence, contracts, riders, and technical specifications.
    - Advertising, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 78)
    - Advertising Collective, Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 79)
    - Clinic, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 80)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 81)
    - Finances, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 82)
    - Fliers, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 83)
    - Forms, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 84)
    - Itineraries, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 85)
    - Land Lease, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 86)
    - Mailing Lists, 1989; Undated (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 87)
    - Maps and Directions, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 88)
    - Messages, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 89)
    - News Clippings, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 90)
    - Notes, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 91)
    - Performers, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 92)
    - Performers, Acoustic Medicine, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 93)
    - Performers, Rory Block, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 94)
    - Performers, Bright Morning Star, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 95)
    - Performers, Casselberry-Dupree, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 96)
    - Performers, David Darling, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 97)
    - Performers, Edwina Lee Tyler & A Piece of the World, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 98)
    - Performers, Kay Gardner, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 99)
    - Performers, Mary Gemini, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 100)
    - Performers, Ruth Pelham, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 101)
    - Performers, Evi Seidman, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 102)
    - Performers, Cathy Winter, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 103)
    - Presenters, Margaret Adler, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 104)
    - Presenters, AmyLee, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 105)
    - Presenters, Donald J. Barnes, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 106)
    - Presenters, Luc Bodin & Anna Bond, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 107)
    - Presenters, Greta Bro, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 108)
    - Presenters, Laura Chester, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 109)
    - Presenters, Christopher Childs, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 110)
    - Presenters, Merrit Clifton, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 111)
    - Presenters, Diane Connelly, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 112)
    - Presenters, Sandra Boston deSylvia, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 113)
    - Presenters, Judith Enck, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 114)
    - Presenters, Rosemary Gladstar, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 115)
    - Presenters, Chellis Glendinning, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 116)
    - Presenters, Elizabeth Dobson Grey, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 117)
    - Presenters, Richard Grossman, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 118)
    - Presenters, Amtul Hannan, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 119)
    - Presenters, Merle Hoffman, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 120)
    - Presenters, Pat Hynes, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 121)
    - Presenters, Jennifer Justice, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 122)
    - Presenters, Kim Karkos, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 123)
    - Presenters, Ynestra King, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 124)
    - Presenters, Winona LaDuke, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 125)
    - Presenters, Eleanor LaCain, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 126)
    - Presenters, Deborah Lee, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 127)
    - Presenters, Medicine Story, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 128)
    - Presenters, Susan Meeker-Lowry, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 129)
    - Presenters, Ingrid Newkirk, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 130)
    - Presenters, Baba Olatunji, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 131)
    - Presenters, Oriethyia, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 132)
    - Presenters, Sarah Pirtle, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 133)
    - Presenters, John Robbins, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 134)
    - Presenters, Brant Secunda, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 135)
    - Presenters, Merlin Stone, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 136)
    - Presenters, Jake Swamp, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 137)
    - Presenters, Luisah Teish, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 138)
    - Presenters, Nancy Jack Todd, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 139)
    - Presenters, Adam Trombly, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 140)
    - Presenters, Jeff Volk, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 141)
    - Presenters, Susan Wood, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 142)
    - Presenters, Ann Wiseman, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 143)
    - Program, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 144)
    - Registration Packet, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 145)
    - Supplies, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 146)
    - Ticket Forms, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 147)
    - Vendors, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 148)
    - Work Crews, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 149)
    - Work Exchange Applications, 1989 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 150)
  - Gay Games IV, 1982-1994, Undated; 2.3; 2.2 cubic ft.
    This subseries primarily consists of promotional materials generated during Michelle Crone's position as Events Director of the Cultural Festival at Gay Games IV in New York City. This includes of programs, publications, fliers, meeting notes, and correspondence. Proposal files include clippings of quotes, reviews on prospective performers, and often contain completed submission forms.
    - Application Video to the 1994 Gay Games Cultural Festival New York from Te Waka Awitina Tane, Inc., ca. 1994 (Vhs 8)
    - Athlete Registration Book, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 151)
    - Buttons and medals, ca. 1994 (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 2)
    - Calendar of Events, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 152)
    - Collared shirt - Gay Games IV, ca. 1994 (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 1)
    - Cultural Festival, Information Pack, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 153)
    - Cultural Festival, posters, 1994 (Oversized 2, Folder 20)
    - Cultural Festival, program with marginalia, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 154)
    - Draft Program, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 155)
    - Dress Suits to Hire, Cultural Festival Drop off, 1993 (Vhs 9)
    - Event Lists, 1994 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 156)
    - Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 8 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 157)
    - Claudette L'Heureux, Equipe Montreal '94, Cultural Festival Call for Entries - Gay Games IV, 1993 (Vhs 10)
    - Large sign for Gay Games IV Cultural Festival on foam core, handwritten schedule on back (24in by 36in), 1994 (Flat-file 2)
    - Large sign for Gay Games IV Cultural Festival on foam core (24in by 36in), 1994 (Flat-file 3)
    - Nametag, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 1)
    - News Clippings, Articles, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 2)
    - Notes, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 3)
    - Organizational Structure, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 4)
    - Monica Palacios, Latin Lezbo Comic Performance Piece (40 min), 1992 (Vhs 11)
    - Performances, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 5)
    - Performers and Performance List, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 6)
    - Performers, Lisa Kron, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 7)
    - Performers, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 8)
    - Photographs, Michelle Crone, 1994 (Box 9 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 9)
    - Planet Q, 1994 (Vhs 12)
    - Plastic Cups - Unity '94, 1994 (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 3)
    - Plastic Flag - Unity '94, Games Can Change the World, 1994 (Box 26 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 4)
    - Poster - Gay Games II San Francisco, 1986 (Roll 2, Folder 2)